ILGWU Justice Photographs 5780/102 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Western States Region - California (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Includes: LA ILGers at picnic in Lincoln Park- with Cornelius Wall and Max Wolf; children in sack race at picnic; entertainment by Mariachi band and dance troupe- 11/1/75; wife of Sol Chaikin- Rosalind receives corsage from LA local; Sol Chaikin addresses membership meeting at Regency Hyatt Hotel- 9/27/75; Sol Chaikin receives proclamation from Mayor Tom Bradley- 11/1/75; Chaikin speaks with and meets strikers from the Great Chinese-American sewing co.- 11/1/75; display of Chinese music and dance; fashion show- 11/1/75; Max Wolf introduces Chai Hong Mock- 11/1/75; Chaikin and wife Rosalind at membership rally at Masonic Temple- with William Wong- 10/8/75; Mattie Jackson at San Francisco ILGers at picnic- 9/15/75; Willie March and daughter at picnic- 9/15/75; United Farm Workers leader Cesar Chavez in LA ILGWU Joint Board Hall with supporters raising flags- 8/15/75; VP Mattie Jackson- manager of San Francisco Joint Board visits with Clara Steinberg- with Paul Steen- chairman of joint board retirees club- 7/1/75; picketers outside of San Francisco Shirt Works- 7/1/75; local members who are married at LA Joint Board Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 38
- Western States Region - California (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Includes: workers at Wells-Leigh in LA hold up sign of winning election- 8/1/76; ILGer Juanita Oregano is crowned queen of Filipino Community of Alameda County in CA- Union City Mayor Tom Kateyama does honors- 5/15/76; workers at California Samples celebrate union election win- 8/15/77; picketers outside Dumas and Canez shops in Palmdale's, Lancaster, CA- 5/1/77; VP Cornelius Wall installs new officers at San Francisco Joint Board- including VP Mattie Jackson crown Anne English queen of Union Label Ball- 12/11/77; picket line at Motif Mfg. In East LA- 12/1/78; Local 551 play soccer- 3/1/78; Moab Sportswear workers celebrate NLRB victory- Dora Burgess, Virginia Hurtado, Judith Robertson, and Terry Goode- 4/15/78 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 39
- Western States Region - California (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Includes: Mattie Jackson, William Robertson, Cornelius Wall, Jay Mazur, Eva Addison, and Phil Russo look on as Sol Chaikin cuts ribbon to LA headquarters- 7/1/85; workers at Armak, Inc. in LA picket- 8/79; picket line at Kelvin Internationals- with Assistant Regional Director Paul Strongin- 3/79; workers at Armak and Co. in LA show results of NLRB election- 3/79; photos of white, Asian, and black workers; business agent Larry Mirgon and San Francisco Joint Board Chairman David Daniels are honored in retirement- with Cornelius Wall and Mattie Jackson- 8/79; instructor Lillian Yee helps workers at Koret of California master English- 8/79; VP Cornelius Wall distributes backpay awards to Cristina Zepeda, Lucia Rodriguez, Serafino Haro, and Rafael Yniguez- 8/79; picture of Golden Gate bridge- 8/79; ILGers led by Joseph Danahy, stand outside Glydon Lingerie and picket- 9/80; Western States Organizing Director Phil Russo leads picketing outside Glydon Lingerie- 7/80; Chaikin at Southern California District Seminar with Max Wolf, Cornelius Wall, and Phil Russo- 7/80; workers at Standard Swiss Embroidery in LA protest and picket- 5/81; VP Cornelius Wall celebrates victory for Glydon Lingerie in LA- 5/81; organizing director Phil Russo joins strikers at LeBeau Emblem in LA- 5/81 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 40
- Western States Region - In General (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Includes: California ILGers with Governor Pat Brown- with Sam Otto and Isidor Stenzor and John Ulene- 9/15/66; Governor of Washington Daniel Evans and wife are presented by Eloise Pratt, a diaper with union label- 10/1/66; workers picket a Tabak store who locked them out- 2/1/66; LA organizing staff and Frederick Siems and Cornelius Wall congratulated Mattie Jackson- 9/1/70; Mattie Jackson gets kiss from daughter- 9/1/70; Mattie Jackson taking oath; Mattie Jackson tackling a shop problem with business agent William Wan and Sol Qune Wong Leong; Mattie Jackson tacking an office problem with Mary Ganotese; Cornelius Wall, Frederick Siems, Mattie Jackson and daughter; VP Hubert Humphrey is greeted by VP Sam Otto- Pacific Coast Director- 8/12/68; LA Cloak Joint Board with Sam Otto at installation gathering- 4/1/68; VP Frederick Siems celebrates win at Chic Lingerie- with Ray Brewster, Ralph Smith, and workers- 8/1/70; LA staffer Ray Brewster, Dolores Dorantes, and Gloria Feliciano confer with Chic lingerie workers- 8/15/70; VP Sam Otto was honored on retirement- with Cornelius Wall, Sam Schwartz, Frederick Siems, VP William Ross, and Isidor Stenzor- 2/1/70 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 41
- Western States Region - In General (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Includes: ILGers donating food to Rio Grande Boys Town; workers picket Mode O'Day Mfg. Co.; workers picket Kayser-Roth; David Dubinsky addresses meeting of LA Cloak and Dress and Sportswear Joint Boards- with Morris Bialis, Basil Feinberg, Samuel Otto, Stulberg, Charles Zimmerman, Evelyn DuBrow, and Sigmund Arywitz and John Ulene; Chips star Erik Estrada gives moral support to Hedman Mfg. Co. strikers- with organizers Alex Pendleton and Daniel Silva- 10/79; employees of Salt Lake City, Utah unite on a picket line- 6/15/66; picketers of Judy Bond, Inc.- 7/1/64; Mayor J.D. Braman designates Union Label Week in Seattle, Washington with Eloise Pratt- manager of Local 184 and Sally Sari- VP of union card and Label Council- 9/1/67 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 42
- Western States Region - In General (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Includes: Asian workers picketing Jung San and Lee Mah Companies; Ralph Smith- Western States Region Organization supervisor with Phil Russo explain details campaign- 8/15/74; Asian woman participate in fashion show/ beauty pageant; a worker holds a signs "Where's the Jobs:- 5/84; Toni Castillo- chairlady at Stual Mfg. Runs an ILGWU booth at the AFL-CIO Union- Industries Show at LA- 7/1/78; CA governor Jerry Brown is greeted by Max Wolf and Cornelius Wall- 10/15/78; gen. Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton discusses imports- with Max Wolf and VP Wilbur Daniels- 4/1/78; Assistant Regional Director Paul Stringing speaks-4/1/78; Phil Russo- Western States Region organization director addresses conference- 4/1/78; Max Wolf conducts education workshops- 4/1/78; VP Cornelius Wall joins LA Jt. Board staff as they sign new contract- with Harry LeCover, Phil Leviton, Gloria Feliciano, and Nell Grajeda- 1/80; Joe Razo and Phil Russo testify before President's Select Commission on Immigration and Refugee Policy- 4/80; VP Cornelius Wall and Max Wolf join governor Jerry Brown at signing of garment industry licensing laws- 8/80; VP Cornelius Wall and organizer Cristina Ramirez Vazquez join Glydon Lingerie workers after victory 2/80; Herman Starobin, Ph.D. director of research ILGWU- on T.V.- 5/84; Walter Mondale Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 43
- Western States Region - In General (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Includes: Utah-Arizona District officers are sworn in; Cornelius Wall welcomes delegates to ILGWU Western States Region annual seminar; photo of delegates to conference; VP Mattie Jackson, Evelyn Dubrow, Max Wolf, James Wood, Cornelius Wall, Jim Keysor, Theresa Hughes, and Art Torres; delegates speak at seminar; LA mayor Tom Bradley speaks; photos of picnic at Lincoln Park finished the weekend; Lt. Governor Mervyn Dymally- AFL-CIO Dept. of Organization and Field Services speaks Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 44
- Western States Region (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Includes: At World's Fair in Seattle, WA people hold ILGWU banner of all unions affiliated with AFL-CIO- 10/1/62; VP Cornelius Wall attends soccer practice of team sponsored by ILGWU- 8/15/77; Business Agent Carlo Leone of Utah-Arizona District Council presents a backpay check to Bernice Jacobi- 1/15/79; workers of Spring City Knit Plant in Deming, New Mexico celebrate union's victor- 6/79 Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 45
- Contact Sheets - May 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  May Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 46
- Contact Sheets - June 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  June Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 47
- Contact Sheets - July 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  July Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 48
- Contact Sheets - August, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  August Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 49
- Contact Sheets - September, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 50
- Contact Sheets - October, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 51
- Contact Sheets - November, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 52
- Contact Sheets - December, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 53
- Contact Sheets - January, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 54
- Contact Sheets - February, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 55
- Contact Sheets - March, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 4, ff 56
- Contact Sheets - April, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 1
- Contact Sheets - May, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 2
- Contact Sheets - Contact Sheets - June, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 3
- Contact Sheets - July, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 4
- Contact Sheets - August, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 5
- Contact Sheets - September, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 6
- Contact Sheets - October, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 7
- Contact Sheets - November, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 8
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 9
- Contact Sheets - December - January (#175), 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 10
- Contact Sheets - April (#197-208), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 11
- Contact Sheets - June (#303-311), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 12
- Contact Sheets - August (#317-323), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 13
- Contact Sheets - June, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 14
- Contact Sheets - June/July (#312-315) (23-25 Chinatown Rally I, 6/24/1982) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 15
- Contact Sheets - August, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 16
- Contact Sheets - September (#324-325, 325 thru 330), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 17
- Contact Sheets - October/November (#331-342), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 18
- Contact Sheets - November/December (#343-356), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 19
- Contact Sheets - January, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 20
- Contact Sheets - February (#369-373), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 21
- Contact Sheets - March/April (#374-390) [1 of 2], 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 22
- Contact Sheets - March-April (#374-390) [2 of 2], 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 23
- Contact Sheets - #413-416 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 24
- Contact Sheets - May-June (#391-395), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 25
- Contact Sheets - Photos Front Page Convention, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 26
- Contact Sheets - August (#417-427), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 27
- Contact Sheets - Labor Day NYC (#428-451), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 28
- Contact Sheets - October-November (#452-), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 29
- Contact Sheets Photos Centerfold - September, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 30
- Contact Sheets - November/December (#497-512), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 31
- Contact Sheets Centerfold - December (Eaves Costume Co.), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 32
- Contact Sheets - January/February (#513-524), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 33
- Contact Sheets FrontPage Justice - February, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 34
- Contact Sheets - May (#209-221222-228), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 5, ff 35
- Contact Sheets - March/April (#524-542), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff1
- Contact Sheets - May/June (#543-569) [1 of 2], 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff2
- Contact Sheets - May/June (#543-569) [2 of 2], 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff3
- Contact Sheets - July/August (#570-582), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 4
- Contact Sheets - September/October (#583-), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 5
- Contact Sheets - November/December (#597-), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 6
- Contact Sheets - January/February (#614-628) [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 7
- Contact Sheets - January/February (#614-628) [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 8
- Contact Sheets - March/April (#629-684) [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 9
- Contact Sheets - March/April (#629-684) [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff 10
- Contact Sheets - May (#685-), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff11
- Contact Sheets - Back page - Justice - "Crafted With Pride", 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff12
- Contact Sheets - Centerfold - Justice - February, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff13
- Contact Sheets Photos - Justice - March, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff14
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff15
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff16
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff17
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff18
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff19
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff20
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff21
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff22
- Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, ff23
- Negatives (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 6, loose in the box not labeled
- Voice of the Knitgoods Workers (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Slides, 35mm slide (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Slides, 35mm slide (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Slides, 35mm slide (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Slides, 35mm slide (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Slides, 35mm slide (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Slides, 35mm slide (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Negatives, photograph negative (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Dress Strike 1958 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Cindy Goes Shopping With Mommy (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Commemorating 25th Anniversary of JUSTICE (Menu) (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Contact sheets and negatives - February, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 1
- Contact sheets and negatives - August, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 2
- Contact sheets and negatives - September: [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 3
- Contact sheets and negatives - September: [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 4
- Contact sheets and negatives - October, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 5
- Contact sheets and negatives - November, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 6
- Contact sheets and negatives - December, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 7
- Contact sheets and negatives - January, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 8
- Contact sheets and negatives - February, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 9
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 10
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 11
- Contact sheets and negatives - April, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 12
- Contact sheets and negatives - May: [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 13
- Contact sheets and negatives - May: [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 14
- Contact sheets and negatives - June, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 15
- Contact sheets and negatives - July: [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 16
- Contact sheets and negatives - July: [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 17
- Contact sheets and negatives - August, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 18
- Contact sheets and negatives - September, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 19
- Contact sheets and negatives - October, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 20
- Contact sheets and negatives - November, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 21
- Contact sheets and negatives - December: [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 22
- Contact sheets and negatives - December: [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 23
- Contact sheets and negatives - January, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 24
- Contact sheets and negatives - February, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 25
- Contact sheets and negatives - March, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 26
- Contact sheets and negatives - April, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 27
- Contact sheets and negatives - May, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 28
- Contact sheets and negatives - June, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 29
- Contact sheets and negatives - July, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 30
- Contact sheets and negatives - August, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 31
- Contact sheets and negatives - September, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 32
- Contact sheets and negatives - October, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 33
- Contact sheets and negatives - November, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 34
- Contact sheets and negatives - December, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 35
- Contact sheets and negatives - January, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 36
- Contact sheets and negatives - February, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 37
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 38
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 39
- Contact sheets and negatives - April: [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 40
- Contact sheets and negatives - April: [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 41
- Contact sheets and negatives - May, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 42
- Contact sheets and negatives - June, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 43
- Contact sheets and negatives - July, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 44
- Contact sheets and negatives - August, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 45
- Contact sheets and negatives - September, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 46
- Contact sheets and negatives - October, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 47
- Contact sheets and negatives - November: [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 48
- Contact sheets and negatives - November: [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 49
- Contact sheets and negatives - December, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 7, ff 50
- Contact sheets and negatives - January, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 1
- Contact sheets and negatives - February, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 2
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 3
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 4
- Contact sheets and negatives - April, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 5
- Contact sheets and negatives - May, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 6
- Contact sheets and negatives - June, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 7
- Contact sheets and negatives - July, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 8
- Contact sheets and negatives, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  August
- Contact sheets and negatives - September, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 10
- Contact sheets and negatives - October, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 11
- Contact sheets and negatives - November, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 12
- Contact sheets and negatives - December, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 13
- Contact sheets and negatives - January, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 14
- Contact sheets and negatives - February, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 15
- Contact sheets and negatives - March: [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 16
- Contact sheets and negatives [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  March
- Contact sheets and negatives - April: [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 18
- Contact sheets and negatives [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  April
- Contact sheets and negatives - May: [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 20
- Contact sheets and negatives - May: [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Contact sheets and negatives - June, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 22
- Contact sheets and negatives - July, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 23
- Contact sheets and negatives - August, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 24
- Contact sheets and negatives - September, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 25
- Contact sheets and negatives - October: [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 26
- Contact sheets and negatives - October: [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Was re-housed, formerly box 8, ff 27